vnunited.com 2010-06-23

# Privacy Policy

**This Privacy Policy applied to multiple domains** , _see bottom._

> **THIRD PARTY ADVERTISMENTS**  
>  To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies (such as Google’s Adsense) may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.
> 
>   * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
> 

>   * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
> 

>   * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
> 

> 
> **USE OF COOKIES**  
>  When you view our Web Sites, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a ‘Cookie’ and will help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor a Web Sites to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
> 
> **ANONYMOUS INFORMATION**  
>  We may collect certain non-personal information from your IP address. This information is used only to provide an enhanced on-line experience for our visitors by optimizing our Web pages for your computer (i.e., the identity of your Internet browser, IP address, referral data, platform type, and search terms ). We may also use this non-personal information to determine the total number of visitors to our Web Sitess.

_**This Privacy Policy applied to the following domains.** allcarsvideo.com, allcartoonclips.com, alljewelryinfo.com, allsoftwareinfo.com, anycellphones.com, anmartialarts.com, anymotorcycles.com, anyvideogames.com, asianmoviereview.com, befunnynow.com, besthotitems.com, bestlaptopnow.com, bestmodelingphoto.com, bestwebsitescripts.com, bobliquor.com, celebvideolookup.com, cookingrecipedb.com, diseaseandcures.com, doctruyenaudio.com, doyourealestate.com, ebabyid.com, fastweb24.com, findanapartments.com, fishlookup.com, healthyfoodcookbook.com, historylookup.com, investmmoneytips.com, largecollectibles.com, lawslookup.com, massivemovieclips.com, musicflu.com, myworldleaders.com, reviewall.info, simplyfreegames.com, videosportsbio.com, vietunited.com, vnehow.com, vntophotels.com, vntuvi.com, vnunitedsol.com, worldtraveldb.com, worldweaponsinfo.com, youhow.info_
